{
    "id": "d4ba380e3d8343beb9c0780144fe2ad1",
    "title": "Noun Forms Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "4f9da4be64924df2a9111b76c6c223cc",
            "title": "Noun Forms Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Your ……………………. that I lied is untrue.",
                    "description": "Accusation is the noun. Accuse is a verb and accusative is an adjective.",
                    "answers": [
                        "accuse",
                        "accusative",
                        "accusation"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The butler received the uninvited callers with ………………………..",
                    "description": "Acerbic is an adjective.",
                    "answers": [
                        "acerbic",
                        "acerb",
                        "acerbity"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Man’s first walk on the moon was a stunning technological …………………………",
                    "description": "Achievement is a noun. Achieve is a verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "achieve",
                        "achievement",
                        "achieving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "His …………………………. that he stole the jewels cleared his sister of blame.",
                    "description": "Acknowledge is a verb",
                    "answers": [
                        "acknowledge",
                        "acknowledging",
                        "acknowledgment"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The painting is the museum’s most recent ……………………….",
                    "description": "Acquirement and acquisition are both nouns acquisition is a material possession while acquirement is a personal skill.",
                    "answers": [
                        "acquire",
                        "acquisition",
                        "acquirement"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Speaking Spanish is one of her …………………………",
                    "description": "Acquirement and acquisition are both nouns acquisition is a material possession while acquirement is a personal skill.",
                    "answers": [
                        "acquisitions",
                        "acquirements"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The election campaign led to bitter ………………………….. between the candidates.",
                    "description": "Acrimonious is an adjective  Acrimony is the correct spelling.",
                    "answers": [
                        "acrimany",
                        "acrimony",
                        "acrimonious"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Put more glue on the stamp to increase its …………………………….",
                    "description": "Adherence is the noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "adhesive",
                        "adherent",
                        "adherence"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………. from abroad indicates that war is about to begin.",
                    "description": "Advise is a verb.  Advice is the noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Advice",
                        "Advise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Susan B Anthony was famed for her ………………………… of equal rights for women.",
                    "description": "Advocacy means support. An advocate is a lawyer.",
                    "answers": [
                        "advocacy",
                        "advocate",
                        "advocative"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her finishing school accent is just an ………………………………..",
                    "description": "An affectation is a false mannerism or pretense.",
                    "answers": [
                        "affect",
                        "effect",
                        "affectation"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am proud to pledge ………………………… to the flag and to my country.",
                    "description": "Allegiance means loyalty.",
                    "answers": [
                        "allege",
                        "allegation",
                        "allegiance"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}